Didn't you say
you had a surprise for me, honey?
I do.
I'll film you. Let me film you.
I just came to say hi.
-I don't know how to do this.
- You don't?
Wow, it's cold here. Let's go inside.
- It's freezing.
- Wait.
I mean it, stop. No.
INSPIRED BY TRUE EVENTS
Do you miss me?
Mommy's here.
Mommy's always here.
Come here.
Certain things you'll understand in time.
Others I will tell you.
Just you.
Mrs. Elize!
Marcinha? I didn't hear you come in.
- It's 7 a.m.
- Really?
- Are you going on a trip?
- What?
- I saw the suitcases and…
- Oh, yes. No.
It's… I'm making a delivery. Wine bottles.
- And Mr. Marcos?
- What about him?
- Should I make him breakfast?
- What's with all the questions?
I want you to take her right now
and bring her upstairs to the playroom.
Let's play.
Go. Go.
ELIZE: SHADOWS OF A WOMAN
7 YEARS BEFORE THE CRIME
FAIRY TALE
What is it?
Is my hair messy?
Not at all. You look beautiful.
Do I?
- You're perfect, Blondie.
- Am I?
Yes, you are.
- No!
- No.
Marcos can't come to the phone right now
because he's… very busy.
- Stop that.
- He's busy fucking the love of his life.
- He is, right?
- Really?
Really. Isn't he?
Second round?
Feels so good.
Goddamn it.
- Marcos is busy.
- Give me the phone.
- He's showing me his love.
- Give me that.
And don't get upset.
I have to go. I'm fully booked.
Hi, honey. I'm in a meeting
with my dad. Make it quick.
I'm swamped with work.
I'm going to the airport.
I told you I have an interview today.
Yes.
Your husband is on the list
of Brazil's top businessmen.
Where's your accent from?
It's from São Paulo.
What about my accent? Where is it from?
Estela. Wow, I'm getting really drunk.
- Are you drinking?
- Yeah, to forget.
Well, well. Speak of the devil…
Answer it, silly.
No way. Marcos has everything he wants.
- I'll keep him waiting.
- Yeah, like he needs more power.
- Didn't you see the news?
- What?
Your popcorn vendor
is one of the richest men in Brazil.
- I know. He told me.
- And?
And he's never going to leave his wife.
They have a daughter.
You still don't get
that you won't find a husband here?
- And he's a prince.
- What?
He's not a salesman.
He's the popcorn prince.
Hey, Kelly.
I was thinking…
You look like my daughter, you know?
Thank you.
- Bye, Renan. Good night.
- Elize, are you avoiding me?
- No.
- I need to talk to you.
- I'm not in the mood to talk.
- Quit the drama.
I've been calling you.
- I have a life.
- Is this because of my wife?
- I'm done, Marcos.
- I have a daughter, a wife.
Yeah, right.
I'll put Rafaela in a hospital.
You can't have things your way
all the time.
Come here. I have a surprise for you.
What's this hospital deal?
The psychiatrist suggested it.
Do you like it?
I love it.
It's yours.
No one's ever given me anything.
I want you all to myself. Exclusive.
Trust me.
Look at this blonde
having a taste of Japanese cuisine.
Did you like it?
Look, I swallowed it.
I'll film us. Here, look, babe.
Beautiful.
Gorgeous.
Come on. Come.
Check out this blondie.
Where else are you taking me?
Wherever you want.
We are here in Tuscany.
- Do you like it, honey?
- I love it!
I love you.
Me too.
You snooze, you lose.
It happens.
You're good, you'll learn quickly.
Come. Come on.
I've never met a woman like her.
Marcos…
Crouch down slowly.
That's it.
There.
Aim. Don't feel sorry.
Hold your breath.
Then slide your finger…
Did I get it?
It's still alive.
Finish it off, Elize.
I'll do it.
You?
Well… I killed it, I'll skin it.
What did I tell you?
Have you been hunting for long, Elize?
No.
Marcos is teaching me to shoot.
Yeah, he told me.
Marcos said you're a lawyer.
I'm still studying.
I'm also a nurse.
I have a degree.
I feel like I know you from somewhere.
Your face looks familiar, you know?
Where have you worked? Tell me.
Wow!
Am I being interrogated now?
I just want to get to know
my best friend's girlfriend better.
Heitor.
This one.
- A special one for you.
- Thanks.
Hey, Blondie, how's it going?
Almost done.
Look, Marcos.
Are we in the elevator?
I'm scared!
Hang on, let me get the lights.
Where are you going?
I don't know.
Watch your step. That's it.
- Don't move, okay?
- Okay.
Marcos, where are you?
What's this?
What's this, Marcos?
Her name is Gigi.
Oh, she's beautiful.
Right?
Oh, my God!
- Hi, Gigi.
- Hi.
This is Blondie.
- I've never seen anything so beautiful.
- Yeah.
Hi.
She likes you.
Does she?
Hi.
What is this place?
It's our home. Do you like it?
"Our?"
- Does it have two floors?
- And a pool.
Sauna.
You like it?
I'm a divorced man.
I want to marry you.
You'll quit VipClass.
We can have a baby.
It's a new life, Blondie. Just you and me.
Until the end?
Until the end.
- I've never used this.
- Haven't you wanted to?
- I always wanted to have this.
- Wait, open it later.
Let me show you… this.
Two hundred guests.
Elize, this is beautiful.
- Look at the ring.
- Everything--
Wow! Look at that. It's so shiny.
Too bad he didn't come.
I wanted him to come.
I begged him to, but he's very busy.
And what's his family like?
Oh, his family is nice.
His mom is kind.
His father barely speaks.
Don't know much about his brother.
I like his cousin.
And Marcos…
He's very affectionate.
He's fun.
He's just like us.
You were very lonely, you know?
It's good to have a partner.
To have someone,
a decent man to build a family with.
That's very, very good.
Hey!
Give your uncle a hug.
Oh, you look so cute.
- Auntie…
- Easy!
Let's go to the living room.
I made the dessert you like.
- For you.
- Thanks.
- Hi, honey.
- Hi.
- Not asking for my blessing?
- Bless me.
Bless you.
You look good. You're different.
Hi, Dri.
- Hi, Auntie! I missed you!
- Missed you too!
Do you want to see my new car?
- Our aunt has a car.
- Fancy.
You look so pretty.
You've grown.
Show me this glove.
- Will my hand fit? Yes.
- Shall we go, Auntie?
Look.
Nena, come see my car. Come on.
Hi, Elize.
Elize.
Excuse me.
Is that big car outside yours, Elize?
I can only imagine how hard you must have…
worked to get it.
Well…
Congratulations, honey.
- Don't you ever touch me again, you hear?
- Hey.
If you do anything to them,
I'll cut your dick off. Got it?
- You like it, huh?
- Don't laugh!
Put that down.
- Put it down.
- What? Are you nuts?
Nuts. Your daughter's nuts.
She's nuts.
Mom…
I already told you
to stay away from here.
What do you want, Elize?
Do you want to ruin my marriage?
- You look beautiful.
- I love you.
I love you.
I, Elize…
- Promise to love you…
- …promise to love you…
- …and keep you, Marcos…
…from this day forward.
I, Marcos…
- Promise to love you…
- …promise to love you…
- …and keep you, Elize…
- …from this day forward.
You're Marcos's cousin, huh?
Are you from São Paulo?
Yes, I am.
- I'm from Chopinzinho.
- I know.
It's different from here.
São Paulo is so lively.
- Did you come alone, Marta?
- Hi, Mr. Matsunaga.
Yes, unfortunately,
my family couldn't come.
How was your trip?
Nice. I was a little nervous.
I'm not used to flying.
Anyway, congratulations.
Your son looks overjoyed.
Thanks so much.
Thanks so much for welcoming
my niece into your family so warmly.
She's a true gift, you know?
She's an angel.
Marcos married Elize so quickly
that I thought I'd get a grandchild.
No, no, Mrs. Matsunaga.
- Won't you give me a grandchild?
- I will.
I just…
I just meant that I'm not pregnant.
Not yet.
But Elize always wanted to be a mother.
We really want to have a baby.
- I was telling Lauro--
- Oh, no. Heitor.
- I'll talk to your dad.
- Come on.
Playing the serious husband now, huh?
Marcos skipped the halftime break.
- You went straight into the second half.
- Heitor!
Marcos doesn't follow the family's advice.
- That's true.
- Right, Dad?
Right.
It's his second marriage.
It has to work out, right, Eliza?
"Ze." It's Elize.
- Yes.
- Oh, Elize.
It'll work out.
How about a toast to the newlyweds?
Cheers!
- No, Aunt! You can't say…
- It's kanpai.
- It's kanpai!
- Campari? Campari!
- You're beautiful, congrats.
- Excuse me.
Elize, let me introduce you
to Mr. Alberto.
Marcos is a lucky man.
Hey, Kelly!
You look like my daughter, you know?
Luísa, his daughter.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Uncle Takashi's in the other hall.
Let's go.
- Your hands are cold. What's wrong?
- Nothing.
I want to dance with my wife.
Say that again.
That I want to dance?
No.
That I'm your wife.
You are my wife.
The collection is all yours now.
Look at you, so dangerous.
Take it off.
I'll take it all off.
I like that.
3 YEARS BEFORE THE CRIME
There was a lady sitting behind me
on the plane.
She talked the whole flight. The…
SANDCASTLE
Oh, my God, Elize.
This is my house, Auntie.
There's a pool upstairs.
And this view.
It must be hard to clean all this.
Yeah.
I'm so happy you came to visit us.
Marcos is happy too.
I'm afraid I'll get lost here.
You'll get used to it.
Hi, Mrs. Marta.
Hi, Marcos. How are you?
- How are you?
- I'm fine. I'm great.
Elize was looking forward to seeing you.
Your house is beautiful.
Make yourself at home.
It's a shame I have to go.
- What?
- I'm off to Brasília. Remember?
- You didn't tell me that.
- I did.
- No, you didn't.
- I did, you're confused.
I'm not.
We have a doctor's appointment tomorrow.
It's your doctor's appointment.
Not mine. You're the one having trouble.
- Is this gynecologist good?
- She's the best in São Paulo.
Sometimes it takes time to get pregnant.
That's normal.
Oh! Aunt Marta can go with you.
Sure, I'd be happy to.
See? That's settled.
See you, Aunt Marta.
When will you be back?
In two or three days, I think.
I'll let you know.
I'm gonna take a shower.
Then we'll eat, okay, Auntie?
Auntie? Let's--
She's our pet.
Wouldn't you rather have a dog or a cat?
Oh, she's very tame.
Snakes and children shouldn't mix.
Marcos said he's going to get
two dogs for our baby.
Get rid of the snake,
or she'll eat both dogs and the baby.
Yay! That must be our pizza.
I killed it.
What for?
To eat it.
I didn't know you enjoyed that stuff.
We both do.
Hence, the room full of weapons?
What did you think?
I don't know.
I learned from you.
I killed my first chicken at your house.
I was about ten years old, I guess.
First try, remember?
Killing a chicken and this huge animal
are totally different things.
Well, they're both animals.
Elize?
What about this treatment?
Do you think it will work?
Why do you ask?
He's a man.
They're not as patient as we are.
Three months, no baby.
You're responding well
to the treatment. The tests are great.
Now we just need to get
your husband's tests.
Marcos has a daughter
from his first marriage.
- I'm the problem.
- That means nothing.
Men's levels also change with age.
Without his tests,
it'll be very hard to continue--
Let's continue with the treatment.
I can handle it.
Look.
What do you think?
Surreal. Have you had a taste?
Wonderful.
I think you'll enjoy it.
Heitor was showing me the lot
for the Cuban cigar auction.
The bid for some boxes is 100 grand.
Can you believe it?
Your husband has a remarkable knack.
He only invests in good things.
Profitable things.
Heitor?
Oh, Bianca! My special last-minute guest.
Welcome.
These are my friends. Marcos and Elize.
How are you?
Make yourself at home.
- Do you want a whiskey?
- Yes, sure.
Elize?
- Elize?
- Did he mention me?
- Does Heitor know about us?
- No, he doesn't.
- How did he meet you?
- Through VipClass.
He logged on and paid.
And Marcos? Have you met him?
I haven't met Marcos.
I didn't know you'd be here.
Are you okay?
You vanished.
You look good.
Popcorn princess. I told you.
Yeah, I married Marcos.
I'm happy.
Your skin's been better.
We're trying to get pregnant.
I'm glad you're happy.
No worries, huh? I don't know you.
Eliza, right?
It was our secret.
You exposed me.
You humiliated me
in front of a disgusting jerk.
I didn't mean to.
When did he find out?
What if he told your parents?
Jesus.
This treatment's stressing you out.
You were less paranoid when you drank.
WRONG PASSWORD.
Are you calm now?
Honey…
Can you clean this up?
I'll reply to some emails here.
You work too much.
WELCOME
FROM: VIPCLASS
HELLO, WHORE RIDER!
SICKDICK23 COMMENTED
CLICK TO VIEW
VIPCLASS
HIGH-END ESCORTS
PROFILE: 39, ASIAN, MARRIED
STATUS: VIPCLASS DIAMOND
LAST VISIT: 1 DAY AGO
LIKED
1 DAY AGO
I'VE DECIDED TO HAVE PLEASURE
AND LOVED IT.
VERY SATISFIED
WONDERFUL COWGIRL!
PERFECT
YOUNG, SINFUL FACE.
We did it twice.
The first time, she rode me.
I treated myself and went down on her.
Top model's body.
Classy lady.
She has a nice tan…
I fucked her from behind.
Once in her mouth, once in her pussy
while she rode me.
She likes to fuck. She got on all fours…
Hot, skinny, a sight to behold.
Missionary.
I'll be back for sure.
Blondie, what are you doing?
Are you crazy?
- I read everything.
- Read what?
Your VipClass profile.
Was that the auction
you were talking about last night?
You went through my stuff?
Did you like her tan?
- What?
- The nymphet?
Come on. In her mouth. Right?
Why did you do that?
- Why?
- Yes.
You told me you'd change.
- It was a relapse.
- A relapse?
I'm taking meds to get pregnant,
and you relapse?
And several times!
- Elize, listen.
- I'm not listening!
- Elize.
- Marcos, it's over.
I'm done.
What will you do?
Give up the good life I give you?
Good life, Marcos?
Fuck this life! I wanted a family.
All you want is sex.
You think I don't? You're damaged goods.
- You can't give me a child.
- Fuck you. Enough!
That's for me to say.
You don't own me!
I love you. Elize.
I promise I'll change--
Are you pregnant?
We did it.
I'll take care of us, okay?
Do you forgive me?
THAT MAKES A NEW LIFE BLOSSOM…
…WITH EVERY GESTURE…
AND REVEALS…
She must be hungry.
Why the suitcase?
I have a meeting in Curitiba.
You said we'd have lunch together.
Change of plans.
What's this meeting about?
Company stuff.
Everyone's involved in this sale.
- My dad's on my neck.
- You promised you'd change.
- What?
- You've lied to me once.
Will you let this go?
I won't. I can't take it again, Marcos.
- Elize, seriously.
- Tell me!
You need a psychiatrist.
You're crazy.
You need medication. You're paranoid.
Don't call me crazy!
Then stop acting like it.
It's okay.
It's okay, honey.
Don't you want to get out a bit?
No. Marcos will be home soon,
and we miss Daddy.
Don't you miss Daddy?
There.
Hi, Marcos.
I was just talking about you.
With Clarice, she's here.
Do I have to?
Say hi to your cousin.
Hi, cousin.
See? I told you I was at home.
What? Wait.
Okay. Bye.
- What?
- Another meeting came up.
He'll be back tomorrow.
Daddy's back tomorrow, okay?
Want me to hold her?
Yes, please.
- Honey, wait.
- Come here, honey.
Right.
- Thanks.
- Auntie's cutie-pie.
What's the matter, Elize?
I'm terrified of losing Marcos.
Why are you saying that?
I've lost so much in my life.
My dad cheated on my mom a lot.
Then one day he left.
He abandoned us.
Wasn't it for the best?
You can't get over a thing like that.
Then my mom married a guy
worse than my dad.
My stepfather.
It started when I was about 12.
And it happened until I was 15.
I said no so many times.
I don't want my girl to grow up
away from her dad.
I can't lose my family.
I fought so hard for this.
You won't lose it.
MY FLIGHT WAS CANCELED, DON'T WAIT UP
Honey?
Let's go to bed.
Let me sleep here.
- Let's go to the bedroom.
- I love you.
YOU'RE SO HOT
"I can't wait for you to quit VipClass."
Are you asleep?
Seriously. Come here.
Come here.
Are you going to leave me hanging?
I'm just tired.
You used to spend all night
serving clients in that club.
You were never tired.
You didn't just say that.
Am I wrong?
You have a nanny, a maid,
luxury, a credit card, a car.
What more do you want? Say it.
Fuck!
I don't want to fight.
Should I pay you?
One hundred, two hundred,
three hundred, five hundred.
Take it all, you whore.
I'm not your whore. I'm your wife.
I'm the mother of your child.
That's the problem.
You're leaving me.
Oh, not this again.
You promised you wouldn't treat me
like you treated your ex-wife. You said--
Stop! Enough!
Look at you.
You're hysterical.
I'm afraid to leave my daughter with you.
Go get help.
Crazy bitch.
THE LARGEST
MENTAL HEALTH CENTER IN SÃO PAULO
"Admission"?
"Private room, 680 a day."
"Part-time, 350 per day."
"Medication, 120 to 450."
This is Dani's voicemail.
I can't answer right now.
Leave a message at the tone.
WHERE R U, BABE? R U COMING?
INCOMING CALL
Hello?
Could you get me a martini?
Same for me. Make it a double.
Celebrating?
Trying to cheer up.
A client stood me up
and won't answer the phone.
Well, just look around.
No shortage of clients here, hon.
Are you new here?
Kind of.
I used to come here a lot.
Then I stopped after I went exclusive.
- That's my dream.
- Really?
Oh, it's not that hard.
Just avoid married men.
It's always a trap.
I like married men.
How dangerous.
No, I just think it's easier.
They're always worried about their wives,
so it's less of a headache for us.
I have one like that.
A prince?
Well, sort of.
He says he'll leave his wife for me.
He's obsessed with me.
He gives me gifts, takes me on trips,
treats me to sushi, teaches me about wine.
In his case, I get it.
His wife is kind of out of it.
She's a mental case.
She takes meds, she's a psycho.
They'll have her admitted next week.
So?
He's still in there with her.
This is from when they arrived.
They arrived separately.
If you look closely,
her car's just like yours. Same color.
- They've been there two hours.
- I knew it.
I took pictures. The full package.
Your lawyer will love it.
- Mrs. Elize--
- Go away!
Send me everything, go.
18 HOURS AFTER THE CRIME
WHIRLWIND
Hi, Marcinha.
I went out for a bit. How's the baby?
She's a little warm.
She has a fever, 98 degrees.
Can I give her the usual medicine?
- Yes.
- Twenty drops?
Yes. Is Marcos there?
- No, ma'am.
- Okay, I'll call him. Bye.
Marcinha, how are things?
- Almost 104 degrees.
- 104?
- Did you bathe her?
- Yes, I don't know what else to do.
Okay, I'm heading home. Bye.
Fuck!
Pull over, ma'am.
Good evening.
- Good evening.
- We'll run a check.
What's wrong? Are you nervous, ma'am?
No.
You know what? I really need to get home.
My baby's running a fever.
Could you let me go quickly, please?
License and registration.
Just a minute.
The car's registration is expired.
I could seize the car.
Ask your husband to sort it out.
You're free to go.
- You two, stop right there!
- Thanks.
There! Pull over.
HAS THE FEVER GONE DOWN?
Jesus.
I haven't heard from him in two days.
Let me know if you hear anything. Thanks.
I know you're nervous, dear,
but try to remember. Make an effort.
I've told you what I remember.
Calm down and think carefully.
Even the smallest detail could help.
I woke up to him
rummaging through his things.
What things?
Oh, a carry-on bag.
Some clothes.
Money, laptop, and his cell phone.
- He must've been kidnapped.
- Don't say that.
Marcos disappears
when we're selling the company?
- It's no coincidence.
- Then why hasn't anyone called?
Are you sure he didn't say anything else
before he left?
He said he'd be back late.
That he might not come back.
He leaned over the bed…
and gave me a kiss.
And said that a man's gotta do
what a man's gotta do.
I just want him to be okay, that's all.
Calm down.
That must be the police.
Marcos will turn up.
He will.
There must be a reason.
I'm here for you
if you need anything, okay?
I know.
Don't forget.
Thanks.
Stay calm.
There's still time.
He hasn't made contact yet,
but we're tracking everything.
- Clarice.
- How are you?
- Nice to meet you.
- Elize, Marcos's wife.
- Good afternoon.
Any news?
Chief Aquino told us
they've put out Marcos' photo
and alerted police departments
and hospitals.
The anti-kidnapping unit will track
any ransom calls.
A dark mystery.
Fragments of a body
were left along dirt roads
near the city of São Paulo,
more precisely
in the Caucaia do Alto district,
a rural zone in the city of Cotia,
forming a sinister puzzle.
On the side of one of the dirt roads,
a single leg was found
in a blue trash bag.
TELL ELIZE AND MOM I'M FINE…
City guards have found the missing limb.
The search
for the missing body parts continues.
Hands, arms, and the head.
Crucial pieces to solving this mystery
and identifying the victim.
The police will keep us posted.
We can't wait, it's been nine days.
Marcos sent an email, made deposits,
but can't get to his cell? It's illogical.
There was some activity
in Marcos's bank account.
A large deposit, 15 thousand reais
at a bank in Vila Brasilândia.
It's near the church we go to.
What about the email?
It seems to have come from his laptop.
They'll trace the IP address
and find out where it came from.
Can they do that?
Apparently, yes.
Then he wasn't kidnapped. Marcos is fine.
A mother's intuition.
No!
New blue trash bags
were found in the Cotia area.
This time, the body parts found
were an arm
and the head of a victim
of Japanese descent.
- With the legs, torso, and hips…
- Any ID yet?
- No.
- The agents on the case…
- Calm down, Aunt.
- It's not him.
- No. It's not him.
- Sit down.
- …they weren't
as well-preserved as expected.
The head that was found could therefore
significantly advance the investigation.
Mrs. Elize.
What?
It's about Mr. Marcos.
The identity of the victim
of the brutal crime
that shocked the country is confirmed.
It's Marcos Matsunaga, businessman
and heir to a billion-dollar empire.
The murder happened 16 days ago.
It's unclear if the crime
is linked to the company's sale.
Parts of the body were found
on dirt roads in Cotia.
After identification, the family waits…
- Don't. Take her upstairs.
- …for the body.
We'll be back with more information.
Go. Go.
Chief?
May we come in?
Of course.
Everything okay?
You tell me.
Any news about Marcos?
Stay calm.
We just came to collect
some of his belongings.
That's okay, right?
Are you sure it's him?
We still have to do the DNA test.
What's that?
Standard procedure.
Come with me to the station, will you?
We're recording, okay?
Okay.
State your full name.
Elize Araújo Kitano Matsunaga.
Marital status?
Widow?
What?
Now you are, right?
That was the last time Marcos was seen.
An error?
A system error?
Maybe he took the stairs.
Did he do that often?
Go down the stairs from the penthouse?
What were you carrying?
Nothing important.
Wine bottles.
That's a lot of wine, isn't it? Heavy?
We sold rare wines.
You came back hours later
without the suitcases.
Did you sell them too?
I gave them to the client.
Where is this client? Here in São Paulo?
No.
Near Cotia.
Can you tell me the client's name?
Sure.
But I forgot.
Don't you remember his name?
No, I don't.
But I can check.
Think about your daughter.
What about her?
You want to see her again, right?
Is this a threat?
- I don't get it.
- I'm trying to help.
By taking my daughter away?
I didn't say that.
Chief, please.
Marcos was like you.
He wanted to take
my daughter away from me.
What's worse
than taking a child from a mother?
I loved Marcos.
He promised he'd be different.
Confess, Elize.
Confess.
DAY OF THE CRIME
THE ABYSS
Elize.
Be careful not to lose everything
you fought so hard to get.
Let go of that anger
and drop this crazy idea of divorce.
I'll make some coffee.
- Dr. Camila?
- Hi, Elize.
Any news?
The court may grant
custody of the baby to Marcos.
He comes from an influential family.
You have a past in prostitution.
Who will the court favor?
What about the photos?
And the video of him with that whore?
Those are unrelated to custody.
Betrayal doesn't factor into this.
Alimony will be proportional
to his paycheck,
and Marcos reports a low income.
Elize?
Get away from her, you piece of shit!
- You son of a bitch!
- Get off me!
- Stop it, Elize! Stop! Enough!
- I'll kill you!
- Easy!
- Enough!
- I'll kill you, you bastard!
- Let go of me!
- Are you nuts?
Don't you ever touch my daughter again!
You always find your way back here.
You like teasing me, right?
Did you call Marcos?
I did.
He'll pick us up at the airport.
Are you sure you don't want
to spend the night here?
It's all right now, Auntie.
It's all good now, Auntie.
It's past now.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Nothing.
The flight delay wasn't my fault.
It's not my fault the flight was delayed.
Shall I put her to bed?
Not yet. Don't you want
to play with your daughter?
I still have some work calls to make.
Go on, take her.
- Can you take everything to her room?
- Mm-hmm. Of course.
Your job needs you at this hour?
Working at this hour, Marcos?
Must be the pizza. Go and pick it up.
You go then. And make
all your little calls while you're at it.
Spent all my time caring
for your daughter this weekend.
I spent the weekend
taking care of the baby.
I'm exhausted. I'm not going down.
I'm too exhausted.
I'm not going downstairs.
Then don't.
You can let the pizza get cold.
- Great idea. Good, cold pizza.
- Mm-hmm.
Hey, what have I done? Huh, Marcos?
Tell me before I lose my mind entirely.
What did I do to you, Marcos?
- Tell me, or I'll really lose my mind.
- You can't be happy.
You just can't be happy.
- Me?
- I give you the moon.
- What more do you need?
- You. Here.
The only thing I'm missing is you, Marcos.
I work. It's my damn company.
But I have to work. It's my company!
It's your father's company.
Everyone knows you slack off.
Your brother is the one who works.
You're not your dad's favorite.
Don't take it out on me.
Don't take it out on me
because your old man doesn't love you.
Shut up, okay?
This fucking pizza.
Mrs. Elize?
Are you doing okay?
Yeah.
She's already asleep.
Would you like for me to spend the night?
Should I stay the night, ma'am?
No.
Are you sure? I can stay and help you.
You can go.
I'll be here early tomorrow, okay?
- Call me if you need anything.
- Okay.
- If you need me, call me.
The fuck is this?
Oh, don't you recognize yourself?
Don't you recognize yourself?
You and that stupid whore on TV?
You and the whore on TV?
You followed us?
Followed? No.
I hired a detective and you paid for it.
I'm not the one who can't be happy.
I'm not the one
who can't be happy, Marcos.
You're the one
who can't live like normal people.
You can only get involved
with prostitutes.
You can only date whores!
So, did you scratch the car?
Are you dumb?
Are you dumb? Of course it was me.
Of course it was me.
You gave her the same
goddamn car you gave to me.
You got the same model,
got the same color.
The same model, the same color.
You even took that bitch
to the same restaurant you take me.
You took that bitch to the restaurant
we always go to, our restaurant.
I know everybody there.
I know the guy who valeted her car!
What do you think I am?
A plaything with no emotions?
A whore who got lucky
and now is fantasizing she's a housewife.
I am the wife in this house.
The whore is her!
Shut it. Eat your fucking pizza.
And turn that crap off!
I want a divorce.
I'm moving South.
I'll set an example for my baby.
I'll take my child and be free.
Give her a better example of how to live.
An example?
- Better example?
- Uh-huh.
Auntie Hillbilly
or maybe Momma the Fuck-head?
Anyone is better
than a piece of shit ignored by Daddy
who pays prostitutes
because it lets him pretend he's a man.
Shut up!
That's why Mr. Takashi
is selling the company.
He knows his son is incompetent.
Because he knows
his son is entirely incompetent.
- A coward! You wimp!
- Shut your mouth! You lunatic!
- Wimp!
- Crazy bitch!
- You always call me crazy!
- My lawyers will take care of you.
- Go ahead!
- I'll remove you from my life!
- You're out of my life!
- Fine!
- Move out of here, whore.
I'm talking to you!
I'm taking my daughter.
You won't see her again.
I'm taking my daughter with me!
Now she's your daughter?
Put that shit down.
Put that shit down, you crazy bitch.
You don't have the guts.
- Be quiet.
- You're sick. A paranoid bitch.
You know that?
Your stepfather was right.
You've been a whore since you were a kid.
Police, 9-1-1.
Good evening. This is the police.
Hello? Is anybody…
The natural light makes you glow.
And the view behind you…
- Let's record this. Look, honey.
- No, wait.
Beautiful.
Gorgeous.
My gorgeous.
- Did you really like it?
- I love it.
Tell me the truth. You wouldn't
just tell me that to make me happy, right?
You're not lying, right?
You wouldn't do that to me.
Mrs. Elize?
I told you to keep her upstairs, please!
She needs to breastfeed.
Leave her in the crib.
I'll be right there.
Go to the market
and buy what we need for dinner.
Of course.
Mmm.
Hi, honey.
Assassina!
Piranha!
I don't know
when you will read this, my dear.
I know there are things
you will never understand.
But there are other things…
Thing that I will tell you one day.
But only you.
IN 2016, ELIZE MATSUNAGA
WAS FOUND GUILTY OF MURDERING
AND CONCEALING THE BODY
OF MARCOS KITANO MATSUNAGA.
THE JURY FOUND THAT MARCOS
COULD NOT DEFEND HIMSELF.
THE JURY REJECTED THE CLAIM
THAT THE CRIME WAS MOTIVATED
BY REVENGE OR MONEY.
IN 2019, THE COURT SENTENCED HER
TO 16 YEARS AND 3 MONTHS IN JAIL,
GIVEN HER CONFESSION.
HAVING SERVED 10 YEARS,
ELIZE HAS BEEN ON PAROLE SINCE 2022.
THE MATSUNAGAS WANT TO REMOVE
ELIZE'S LAST NAME FROM THE CHILD,
AND CUT ALL TIES WITH THE MOTHER.
ELIZE NEVER SAW HER DAUGHTER AGAIN,
NOT EVEN IN PHOTOGRAPHS.